--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：心仪Sally
翻译：死神夜月 Flower一休 RK翔 小粥粥 slowly回声 hangubing
校对：心仪Sally 淡定哥
- What do you want?  - Why is this door locked, Andrew?
- 你在干什么?  - 门怎么锁了 安德鲁?
I'm getting ready for school.
我待会就要去学校了
Open this door, Andrew.
开门 安德鲁
- Listen to me.  - No, you're drunk.
- 按我说的做  - 不 你喝醉了
I'm what?
我怎么了?
Excuse me?
你再说一遍?
I said unlock the door.
我说了 开门
Andrew?
安德鲁啊?
Dad, it is 7:30 in the a.m., and you are drunk.
老爸 现在才早上7点半了 你喝醉了
- Listen. You don't tell me if I'm drunk or not, you little shit.  - Aren't you?
- 听着 我醉没醉不用你管 你个臭小子  - 你醉了没?
What are you doing in there, huh?
你在里面搞什么东东 哈?
- I'm filming this.  - Huh?
- 我在录像  - 哈?
- What?  - I bought a camera...
- 你说什么?  - 我买了个摄像机...
and I'm filming everything from here on out.
从现在起 我要录下所有的一起
And it's yours right now for only 46.50! Yeah!
现在你只需要花46.5美元就能拥有它! 没错!
Mom? Mom.
妈妈? 妈妈?
Hey.
嘿
Say hello to my new camera for me.
朝镜头打个招呼
Who's the audience?
你拍给谁看呐?
Just the millions of people that are watching at home.
电视机前成千上万的观众啊
- Do I look awful?  - No, no, no, Mom.
- 我看起来很糟吗?  - 不 不 不 妈妈
You look... You look great.
你看起来... 你看起来起色好极了
- It's a nice camera.  - Well, thanks, Mom.
- 摄像机看起来不错  - 谢谢你 妈妈
So, um, should I ask about the camera or...
那 呃 我该问问这摄像机是怎么回事还是...
Uh, I don't know. I'm... I'm filming things now.
呃 我不知道 我在... 我现在开始录东西了
- I'm filming everything.  - You're filming everything?
- 我要记录身边的一切  - 你要记录身边的一切?
- Yeah.  - Okay.
- 是的  - 好吧
God, make it stop.
天呐 别疯了
Have you ever read any Arthur Schopenhauer?
你读过Arthur Schopenhauer的作品吗?
（阿瑟.叔本华 德国的唯心主义主义大师 ）
No. What is Arthur Schopenhauer?
没有 Arthur Schopenhauer是干什么的?
He's, um... he's this philosopher that I'm reading at the moment.
他是 呃... 他是个哲学家 我最近在看他的作品
- For school?  - No, no.
- 在学校里吗?  - 不 不是
Uh, basically, human beings have to recognize themselves...
呃 从根本上来讲 人都应该意识到自己...
- as beings of pure will, right?  - Okay.
- 是一种单纯意志存在 懂吗?  - 是的
So all emotional and physical desires can never be fulfilled.
人类所生理和心理上的欲望永远不会被满足
So basically you're telling me that I should give up on life.
你刚才的意思是让我放弃生活
- Yes.  - Okay.
- 是的  - 好吧
- Come on, man!  - Oh, God.
- 得了吧 伙计!  - 奥 别唱了
- I'll see you later.  - All right, dude. Peace.
- 回头见  - 好的 哥们 路上小心点
Learning time.
学习时间到了
Get out of the way.
别挡路
Are you not coming in?
你不进学校吗?
I'm gonna hang back a while, okay?
我待会回来 好吗?
Uh, you're gonna be late for first period.
呃 你第一节课会迟到的
This is my school.
这就是我所在的学校
I guess.
算是吧
Vote for Steve, brah!
把票投给史蒂夫 亲们!
Okay.
好吧
Hey, you! Hey, guy. Vote for Steve for senior class president.
嘿 你好! 嘿 伙计 选史蒂夫当高年级学生会主席
- Vote for Steve.  - Yeah, I got it.
- 把票投给史蒂夫  - 好的 知道了
This is where I eat lunch.
这是我吃午餐的地方
Out here on the bleachers.
这边是露天看台
Four, five, six, seven, eight. And one...
4 5 6 7 8 再来 1...
'Cause I don't wanna see anybody pull up... That's right.
我不想看到有人偷懒... 很好
Way to your left. There you go, Jack. That's right. Okay.
往左转 好的 Jack 做的很好 好的
A cohesive unit today.
大家必须团结一心
O-R-Y! V-I-C-T-O-R-Y!
必 胜！必 胜！
I don't want to see any crap out there. All right?
我不想看到任何一个人退出 好吗?
T-O-R-Y!
必 胜!
- Whoo!  - Good job. All right.
- 呜!  - 干的好 很好
Hi.
嗨
Hey.
嘿
Could you not videotape us, please? It's really creepy.
别录了 好吗? 挺诡异的
Uh, no. I wasn't...
呃 不 我不是有意...
- Hi!  - This is the hallway where my locker is.
- 嗨!  - 这里是放置储物箱的走廊
What is this?
这是什么?
What's up, Detmer?
怎么样 德特摩尔?
- Wow, you should be on television. - Man, you're on a film, man.
- 哇哦 你应该上电视啊  - 伙计 你上电影了也 伙计
Pretty on camera.
很上镜嘛
- Smile, man. You look pretty.  - You gonna cry? You gonna cry?
- 笑一个 伙计 你很帅  - 你要了哭吗? 要哭了吗?
Sean, come on. Give it back.
Sean 得了吧 还给我
Huh? You want your camera? Piece of shit from, like, 2004?
哈? 你想要回你的摄影机? 这个好像是2004年生产的烂货?
Here you go. Here she is. In one piece.
给你 还给你 完好如初
- Oh!  - Oh, guys.
- 奥!  - 噢 伙计们
- Assholes!  - Come on!
- 混蛋!  - 走吧!
- All right. You ready to bounce?  - Yeah.
- 好了 闪了吧?  - 好
There's a party tonight.
今晚有个聚会
Okay.
知道了
Haven Hills.
在Haven Hills
Wait. I thought Haven Hills was closed.
等一下 Haven Hills不是关了嘛
It's abandoned, yeah. What, you don't want to go?
它是被废弃了 怎么了 你难道不想去吗?
No.
不想
- When was the last time you went to a party? - I don't go to parties.
- 你上次参加聚会是什么时候?  - 我不参加聚会
- You're a senior. You are a senior.  - I don't go to parties.
- 你是学长 你是学长啊  - 我不参加聚会
- Just come.  - I'll think about it, okay?
- 来吧  - 我考虑一下 行了吧?
Okay.
行
But when we go tonight, Andrew, can I give you, like, a pro tip?
安德鲁 如果你真要去 我能给你提条 专业性意见么?
What?
什么?
Maybe leave your camera at home.
别带你的摄像机来
- Why?  - Because it's a little weird.
- 为什么?  - 因为带着的话 看着有点怪
It serves a purpose.
我带它是有目的的
I'm... I'm just trying to be a good cousin here, okay?
我... 这是我做为好表兄的职责 好吗?
This is me being your friend and telling you...
这是一个好朋友的忠告...
you should probably not take the camera to a party.
参加聚会不能带摄像机
Okay.
知道了
This is my street.
这是我家所在的街道
And those are the official douche bags of my street.
那几个是这条街道上的小混混
- What the hell's that?  - Oh, great.
- 他在搞什么?  - 奥 糟了
Hey! What you doing? Andrew!
嘿! 你在干什么? 安德鲁!
- No, I wasn't...  - Don't film me, Detmer! Don't film me.
- 不 我不是...  - 别拍我 德特摩尔! 别拍我
Run to your house, bitch!
滚回家去 混蛋!
This is where I eat lunch.
这是我吃午餐的地方
Out here on the bleachers.
这边是露天看台
What do you want?
你想干什么?
When I say open that door, you open the door. You got it?
我让你开门 你就开门 听到了吗?
Finish your goddamn homework.
赶紧把你作业做完
- Matt, are you sure it's here?  - Dude, it's here.
- 马特 你确定是这儿吗?  - 哥们 就是这儿
Calm down, okay?
冷静点 好吗?
Oh, yeah.
奥 是这儿
Wow. Look. A rave.
哇哦 瞧 多热闹啊
Oh, wow. Look. A nerd with a camera.
奥 哇哦 瞧 带着摄像机的白痴
- What?  - Just don't follow me around all night, okay?
- 什么?  - 别整晚跟着我 行吗?
What do you mean? I thought...
什么意思? 不是你...
I thought you wanted me to come with you.
是你让我跟你一起来的
I did. I did. But just go and do your own thing for once, okay?
是的 是的 你也试着去干点自己的事 好吗?
Just... have a beer, talk to people.
就去... 去喝一杯 找个人聊聊天
I don't drink.
我不喝酒
Hey! Hey!
嘿! 嘿!
Hey!
嘿!
Excuse me. Hey! Hey, what are you filming for?
借过 嘿! 嘿 你在拍些什么啊?
Oh, I don't... Um...
奥 我没... 嗯...
- Uh...  - What?
- 嗯...  - 你说什么?
- I can't hear you.  - I'm just filming.
- 我听不到你说话  - 我只是随便拍拍
- Oh. Oh, cool. Cool. I'm filming for my blog.  - Oh.
- 噢 噢 酷 我是想录一段上传到我的博客上去  - 噢
- Andrew. Andrew.  - You should check it out. It's actually...
- 安德鲁 安德鲁啊  - 你应该过来看看 实际上...
- Oh, hey. Hey, Casey.  - Hey.
- 奥 嘿 嘿 Casey  - 嘿
- How you doing?  - I'm good. I'm good.
- 最近怎么样啊?  - 很好 我很好
This is pretty lame, right?
这个聚会很没劲 是吧?
Why is it lame?
为什么说它没劲啊?
You know, Jung said parties are just...
你知道 Jung曾说过 聚会只是...
（卡尔.荣格 分析心理学的创立者）
people's way of seeking widespread validation.
人们寻求集体认同的一种方式
I'm not one to clamor to be cool, you know.
我不是在这里喧闹扮酷的 你知道的
Wow. Way to put an analytical psychology spin on this barn party, Matt.
哇哦 马特 你的分析心理学还真是活学活用啊
That's awesome.
这太棒了
Awesome.
很棒
- You're awesome.  - Hey, Matt.
- 你也很棒  - 嘿 马特
Hey, what did Jung say about glow sticks?
嘿 Jung是怎么评价荧光棒的?
You filming my girlfriend?
你在拍我的女朋友?
Yes or no?
是还是不是?
No, I... I'm not filming anything.
不是 我... 我什么也没拍
- I'm just filming the party.  - Okay.
- 我在拍这个聚会现场  -  好吧
I should break your bitch-ass nose. You know that?
我现在应该打断你的鼻子 你知道吗?
- No, I wasn't...  - Don't talk back to me.
- 不 我没拍...  - 别顶嘴
- Bitch.  - Okay.
- 混蛋  - 好的
Andrew?
安德鲁啊?
Andrew.
安德鲁啊
With the camera.
拿摄像机那个人
- Can we... can we use that thing?  - What?
- 可以... 可以借用一下它么?  - 什么?
We found the craziest shit, and we gotta get it on tape.
我们发现了疯狂的一幕 我们得录下来
- Uh, it's not...  - What's up, man?
- 呃 这不是... - 怎么了 哥们?
- You okay?  - Yeah. I'm... I'm Andrew.
- 你还好吗?  - 是的 我... 我是安德鲁
Okay. I'm Steve.
我是史蒂夫
- Steve Montgomery.  - Yeah, I know.
- 史蒂夫.蒙哥马利  - 是的 我知道
Really?
真的吗?
Matt and I were just hanging out...
马特刚刚和我一起乱晃...
and we found this cool little...
我们发现了一个很酷的东西...
- this thing.  - Wait. You're with Matt?
- 这种东西  - 等一下 你跟马特在一块儿?
- You might want to get it on tape. - No,I just, I don't really...
- 你可能想录下来 - 不 我只是 我真的不想...
Dude, just come on. Just come get it on tape. It'll be cool.
伙计 来吧 录下来 很酷的
- I don't know.  - Trust me.
- 我不确定  - 相信我
- All right.  - Yeah, man.
- 好吧  - 就该这样 伙计
You know there are, like, tons of girls around here, right?
你知道这里有很多女孩 是吧?
And you're all by yourself next to a tree?
你却自己独自一人待在树旁?
I'm just really picky.
我有点挑剔
- Listen. I really don't think...  - Is there a light on that thing? Like, on the camera?
- 听着 我真不觉得...  - 那上面有灯吗? 摄像机上?
Uh, yeah. Here.
是的 有
What were you guys doing out here?
你们这帮人在这里干什么?
A bunch of people were out here
一大帮人都出来了
'cause we were, like, obsessed with the thing.
他们就像对这个东西着迷了一样
What thing?
什么东西?
You'll see.
待会你就看到了
Oh, that's... that's right! Andrew Detmer!
奥 对... 我想起来了! 你是安德鲁・德特莫尔!
I remember you from homeroom, freshman year.
高一的时候 我在年级教室见过你
You always had that gray zip-up hoodie.
你老是穿着那件灰色有拉链的连帽衫
- Garetty!  - You remember that?
- Garetty!  - 你还记得这个?
Yeah, I got a... I got a thing for faces, which is why I'm going into politics.
是啊 我... 我对见过的人过目不忘 正因为这我才搞政治
Ironically enough, 'cause I'm so ridiculously hi...
挺讽刺的 因为我实在...
- Down here!  - Ah, there we go.
- 下来!  - 啊 我们走吧
- Garetty, what's up? I see you!  - Matt!
- Garetty 你在搞什么 我看到你了!  - 马特!
- You see me?  - Yeah, where did everybody go?
- 你看到我了吗?  - 是的 大家都跑哪儿去了?
They left! They left! Come on. Let's go, let's go, let's go!
他们走了! 他们已经走了! 下来 快快快!
- Do you see that?  - Guys, what is that?
- 你看到那个了吗?  - 伙计们 那是什么?
- Do you see it? Is that the camera?  - Yeah, I got him!
- 你看到了吗? 那是摄像机吗?  - 是的 我把他带来了!
- Do you guys know how to get back from here?  - Is it still making that sound?
- 你们知道怎么回去吗?  - 它还在发出那种响声吗?
- Yes. Did you tell Andrew? - Andrew,it's making that sound, dude.
- 是的 你跟安德鲁说了吗?  - 安德鲁 听 这响声就是它发出来的
Dude, come and listen to this. Listen to this.
伙计 过来听听这个 仔细听
- No, no, no, no. You gotta get in.  - Okay, okay.
- 不 不 不 不 不 你得靠近点听  - 好的 好的
You gotta get close, like literally almost in the hole.
你得靠近点 贴在洞口边听
Okay, don't push me. Just don't push me.
好的 不要推我 我自己过去
- Check this shit out.  - We're not gonna push you in.
- 听一下  - 我们不推你
We're just trying to get it on camera.
我们得录下这个
- Listen. Can you hear that?  - Shh, shh.
- 听 你能听到吗?  - 嘘 嘘
What...
什么...
I think we got it.
应该录下来了
Wait. How creepy is that?
等一下 这多吓人啊?
Is this sound coming up?
是从下面传来的声音吗?
I don't know. I mean, probably. It's pretty loud, right?
我也不知道 我是说 可能吧 声音的确很大 是吧?
- Hello!  - All right, dude. We're going inside.
- 喂!  - 好的 伙计 我们下去看看吧
- I'm going back. Come on, you guys.  - I gotta know.
- 我要回去了 走吧 伙计们  - 我得下去看看
Matt, seriously, we... Hey, wait, wait. Steve!
马特 别开玩笑了 我们... 嘿 等等 等一下 史蒂夫!
Steve!
史蒂夫来啦!
Oh, shit. He's a ninja.
奥 混蛋 他像个忍者一样
Matt...
马特啊...
Whoa, Matt, Matt, Matt. What are you doing?
哇哦 马特 马特 马特 你在干什么?
Are you serious?
你开什么玩笑?
- Andrew, can you give me some light?  - Matt, don't be an idiot.
- 安德鲁给我照一下?  - 马特 别犯傻了
Whoop! Whoop!
喔噗! 喔噗!
Matt! Matt, you're my ride home!
马特! 马特 你还得开车送我回家呢!
Hello?
能听到吗?
Oh!
奥!
Smells terrible. You guys!
真难闻 伙计们!
Matt!
马特啊!
Hello?
有人吗?
Andrew's such a pussy.
安德鲁像个娘们一样
All right. Does it go down much deeper, or what?
行了 这通向更深的地方 还是什么?
Yeah, man. It goes really, really far.
是的 伙计 它确实会通向很远很远的地方
Andrew, bring the light.
安德鲁 打好灯光
Look at the walls. It's like a straight shot down.
你看这墙 几乎是垂直的
Probably already come like 40 or 50 feet.
我们大概已经走了40或50英尺了
Yeah, just don't talk about it, okay?
别再说了 行吗?
You ever... you ever heard of Plato's "Allegory of the Cave"?
你曾经... 听说过柏拉图的"洞穴之喻"吗?
I don't know, Matt. Let's just get this over with.
没听过 马特 继续往里面走吧
Oh, shit!
哦 见鬼!
Holy shit.
天呐
What the hell is that?
这是什么玩意儿啊?
Matt, I'm not kidding. I can't breathe.
马特 我是认真的 我感觉呼吸困难
- Come on.  - Andrew, look at this.
- 快跟上  - 安德鲁 快来看
What
什么
Can you believe this?
你能相信这一切吗?
Matt.
马特啊
What am I looking at?
这是什么玩意儿啊?
- Ah, shit!  - I am freaking out right now!
- 啊 见鬼!  - 我好害怕!
Matt! Can we get out of here, please?
马特! 快走吧 求你了
Is it showing up on the camera like that?
摄像机里也是这样显示的吗?
I don't know, man.
我不知道
It's messing with it. I don't really want to film
受到干扰了 我不想拍
Dude, I'll buy you a new one.
哥们儿 我会再给你买台新的
Touch one.
摸一下
Matt!
马特啊!
- Matt, look at this!  - What?
- 马特 快来看!  - 怎么了?
Look at this!
快来看啊!
Dude, what is
哥们儿 这是什么
Dude, no way!
哥们儿 不会吧!
- It's changing colors!  - Oh, my God.
- 它还在变颜色!  - 哦 天呐
Must be reacting to heat.
肯定是感受到了外界温度的变化
- I can't hear you over that...  - This is awesome.
- 我听不清你...  - 太酷了吧
Oh! Dude, your nose!
哦! 哥们儿 你的鼻子!
Steve, Steve!
史蒂夫 史蒂夫啊!
Steve!
史蒂夫啊!
Matt, dude, put your phone down. Turn it off.
马特 把手机拿下去 关了它
- Okay, okay, okay.  - Steve, you too.
- 好的 知道了  - 史蒂夫 你也是
- All right.  - We have to document this.
- 好吧  - 我们得把这一刻给记录下来
- Okay. Are you guys ready?  - Yeah. I'm ready.
- 好了 你们准备好了吗?  - 嗯 准备好了
- All right. Here we go. Okay, Steve  - What?
- 好了 开拍 史蒂夫啊  - 怎么了?
Can you move to your left?
能往左边靠一下吗?
- Here?  - Um, yeah. That's good.
- 站这儿可以吗?  - 呃 行 很好
And then, Matt
然后 马特
can you just go right in front of Steve?
你能站到史蒂夫前面吗?
Um
呃
- Here?  - Yeah, perfect. Yeah, yeah. Okay.
- 这儿吗?  - 是的 很好 就那儿 好了
This is the ball test.
现在开始进行棒球测试
- You ready?  - Yep.
- 准备好了吗?  - 好了
Oh!
哦!
What the shit, Steve?
搞什么鬼 史蒂夫?
Get off! Get off! What are you doing? Underhand.
别碰我! 手拿开! 让你投下手球的嘛
I tried, man. I tried.
我是这么想来着
- Let's do it. Let's do it.  - All right.
- 再来一次  - 好吧
- All right. Wait, wait.  - We good?
- 好了 等等  - 准备好了吗?
- We said underhand, right?  - Yeah, it is underhand. Yeah.
- 说好的是下手球 对吧?  - 没错 是下手球
Okay.
好的
- Underneath.  - I'm on you. You're not gonna get me this time.
- 下手球  - 我准备好了 这次不会让你砸到我了
- You ready?  - Yeah.
- 准备好了吗?  - 好了
- I'm on it. Yeah.  - I don't know what you're talking about.
- 我准备好了  - 不知道你在说些什么
Let's go.
来吧
Oh!
哦!
Yeah! The crowd goes wild!
耶! 大家欢呼吧!
- Yeah, I'm ready. All right.  - Matt, beam him. Beam him.
- 好了 我准备好了 来吧  - 马特 砸他
- I'm... I'm going to.  - Beam him.
- 我... 我会的  - 砸他
Oh!
哦!
- Oh!  - No way! Shit!
- 哦!  - 不会吧! 天呐!
Wait, wait, wait. That's great!
等等 帅呆了!
- He did it!  - I did it! I did it!
- 他做到了!  - 我做到了! 我做到了!
- That is crazy!  - Oh, my God!
- 太不可思议了吧!  - 哦 天呐!
- Look at it!  - Oh, my God!
- 快看啊!  - 哦 天呐!
- Holy shit!  - Oh, my God.
- 见鬼了!  - 哦 天呐
- Oh, my God.  - Oh, dude, you're bleeding. You're bleeding.
- 哦 天呐  - 哦 哥们儿 你在流鼻血啊
- Oh, man, shit.  - Stop, stop, stop. Get a tissue.
- 哦 见鬼  - 快停下 拿张纸巾
You did it! Yes!
你成功了! 太棒了!
- Put on the music.  - Oh, yeah.
- 放首歌  - 哦 耶
Yes.
太棒了
Matt, you have... you have to pretend like you're squeezing them together with your hands.
马特 你... 你得装作是在用手用力挤它们
That's what I'm doing. Look. That's what I'm doing.
我就是这么做的 瞧 我就是这么做的
I can't do it, dude. I give up.
我做不到 哥们儿 我放弃
You do it. You're better at this than I am.
你来吧 你比我厉害
Oh, really? Am I? Really?
哦 真的吗? 我真的比你厉害?
Just do it.
快来吧
Oh.
哦
Sick.
见鬼了
Dude, I hate you! That's
哥们儿 我恨你! 简直
- I'm impressed, man. I am impressed.  - That's amazing.
- 我服了 哥们儿 真服了  - 太棒了
That was awesome, dude.
太棒了 哥们儿
- Oh, no!  - Come on, dude.
- 哦 不!  - 拜托 哥们儿
- That is not cool.  - What?
- 这样就不地道了  - 什么?
- That is not cool.  - My Legos.
- 这么做不太地道啊  - 这是我的乐高啊
You've been hanging out with those two guys for the last three weeks.
过去三个星期里你一直在和那两个小子鬼混
- "Three weeks."  - I'm not stupid.
- "三个星期了"  - 我不是傻瓜
I think you're hiding something from me. You better call me back.
你肯定有事瞒着我 快给我回电话
- Wow.  - I love you.
- 哇  - 爱你
I'm gonna get a brick through my window. I am legitimately scared.
有人要用砖头砸我家窗户 我害怕极了
I have an election coming up, and I don't have time for this.
我马上就要去参加选举了 我没时间继续玩了
Dude, why are you asking us for advice on girls?
哥们儿 你怎么向我们问起泡妞经验啦?
Because we're his mistress.
因为我们都是他的基友啊
So, what, you think it's, like, radiation or something?
什么 你觉得这是因为辐射还是其它什么原因?
- Radiation from what?  - Dude, it's the government.
- 从哪儿来的辐射?  - 哥们儿 这事和政府有关
What? Matt, what are you talking about?
什么? 马特 你在说什么啊?
I'm feeling pretty spelunked out actually.
我觉得和那次洞穴之旅有关
Andrew, relax.
安德鲁 淡定
That's so weird. It looks completely different during the day.
太诡异了 这里的情形在一天之内完全变了样
Look. I don't care, okay? I am not going in the hole again.
我才不管这么多呢 我不会再到那个洞里去了
Asshole.
混蛋
It's like sunk in or something.
就好像突然沉没了
- There goes your old camera, dude.  - Oh, shit.
- 你的摄像机就这么没了 哥们儿  - 哦 见鬼
That's weird. I can still feel it down there.
太奇怪了 我还感觉得到它就在下面
I can't believe we made it out of there.
真不敢相信我们逃了出来
Well, I mean, that answers that, right?
这一切就不言自明了 对吧?
Um, what does? We still don't know what happened.
呃 什么? 我们还是不知道发生了什么
- No  - Well, we're still alive.
- 不  - 我们还活着
- I mean, I was definitely  - Hey!
- 我是说 我真的  - 嘿!
You kids can't be here, okay?
这儿不是玩的地方 知道吗?
- You gotta move on out.  - What?
- 你们得离开这儿  - 什么?
The ground's unstable. We're taping the whole place off.
那地方不稳定 那地方是禁止进入的
Okay. We're going.
好吧 我们这就走
Vote for Steve!
为史蒂夫投票哦!
New camera's working out for you. That's good.
你的新摄像机用的还挺顺手吧 不错噢
Yeah, it's pretty cool, right?
简直酷毙了
- Yeah, smaller.  - Does that shoot on tape?
- 这台小了些  - 也是拍在录像带上的吗?
No, it just... It, like, records right onto the camera.
不 是直接储存在摄像机上的
No, I just want to record all the stuff that we can do, you know.
不是 我只想记录下我们所能做的一切
Yeah, but it's like all the time.
是吗 但是你得一直带着摄像机啊
You don't feel like it's a little weird
你不觉得有点诡异吗
Like it puts a barrier between you and everything else?
就像是它在你和其它东西之间建起了一道屏障
Uh, I don't know.
呃 我不知道
Maybe I want a barrier.
或许我想要有一道屏障
So, like, what's up with your dad?
跟我说说你爸的情况吧
What's his story? What does he do?
他是做什么的?
Um, my dad's a firefighter.
呃 我爸是一名消防队员
Okay. That's cool. Oh, man, that must have been awesome
很酷嘛 哥们儿 那样子肯定很帅
Yeah, well, he was, I guess.
我想是的吧
- What happened?  - Uh, I don't know. He didn't die or anything.
- 怎么了?  - 呃 我不知道 他活得好好的
He just... he got injured on the job, and now he, um
他只是... 他在工作时受了伤 他现在 呃
he collects the insurance, you know.
现在靠赔偿金生活
Um, so he doesn't really do anything.
呃 他现在无所事事
He just... he, um... he'll go out during the day, but I don't know where he goes.
他只是... 他 呃... 他白天都在外面 我不知道他去了哪儿
Uh, he drinks a lot.
呃 没日没夜地喝酒
I know that much.
我只知道这么多
Yes. Karen Detmer. D-E-T-M-E-R.
没错 凯伦.德特莫尔 D-E-T-M-E-R
Yes. Thank you.
是的 谢谢
She's in pain.
她很痛苦
She needs something stronger.
她需要药效更强一点的
Her breathing's worse.
她呼吸越来越困难了
Sir, she's suffering.
先生 她痛苦极了
Please help me.
求你帮帮我
I'm on disability. I can't afford $700.
我是个残疾人 我付不起700块
Please, don't put me on hold! She can't breathe, okay?
求你了 不要不理我啊! 她无法呼吸了?
I don't know what to do anymore.
我不知道怎么办了
Is it on?
在拍吗?
Yeah. Yeah. You got it.
在拍 你说对了
I want to remember you like this.
我想记住你现在的摸样
Oh, Mom.
哦 妈妈
You're stronger than this.
你可以比现在更加坚强
Can you say that for me?
能为我说一遍吗?
Please?
求你了
I'm stronger than this.
我可以比现在更加坚强
Oh, nice.
哦 真棒
All right. Here. Watch this.
好了 瞧着
- Weak.  - Hey, Matt.
- 好衰  - 嘿 马特
Yeah?
什么事?
Do you like me?
你喜欢我吗?
Um, yeah, of course.
呃 当然了
I mean, you know, I didn't...
我是说  我不是
- I mean, you know, I didn't always.  - What do you mean?
- 我是说 我不是一直这样  - 什么意思?
I don't know. Like, you haven't
我不知道 比如 你不是
you haven't always been super-easy to talk to, you know.
一个容易沟通的人
I mean, I'm not saying that you're not now. I'm just
我不是说你现在不容易沟通 我只是
You're such an asshole.
你这个混蛋
That's what I'm talking about, dude. You're hostile, see?
我就是这个意思 你充满敌意 明白了吗?
Better.
好点了
- Hey, Matt.  - Yeah?
- 嘿 马特  - 怎么了?
Do you ever think about, like
你有没有想过 比如
doing more with it?
用它来干一些其它事情?
What, with this?
什么 用它吗?
Not really.
还真没想过
Why? What else is there?
怎么了? 那儿还有什么?
- "Telekinesis."  - Yes. Do tell.
- "心灵遥感"  - 知道 这还用你说
"The ability to move, lift, vibrate"
"移动 悬空 震动的能力"
That's my favorite.
真是我最喜欢的部分
"Spin, bend, break or impact objects...
"通过意念或其他非物理方法的直接影响
through the direct influence of mental power or other nonphysical means."
对物体进行旋转 弯曲 或者破坏"
- Okay.  - Sounds familiar.
- 好吧  - 听起来很熟悉
- It does sound familiar.  - Very familiar.
- 确实很熟悉  - 非常熟悉
You want to see direct influence?
你想见识一下直接影响吗?
Andrew.
安德鲁啊
She's wearing black today.
她今天穿的黑色内裤
- Hi.  - That's direct influence.
- 嗨  - 那就是直接影响
- ...week, in my room.  - Just listen.
- ...我在房间里  - 听好了
I'm just that much stronger. Even last night I got my whole bed off the ground.
我变得越来越强了 昨晚我让床都飘了起来
- No nosebleed.  - Yeah? I've been lifting weights too.
- 没有留鼻血  - 是吗? 我也能让重物飘起来
This is my theory though is that it's like a muscle.
我觉得这就像是肌肉
Like, it's elastic. If you stretch it too far, too quick, it'll tear.
还具有弹性 如果你伸展得太远或者太快 都会撕裂
Ew.
是嘛
That's why I think we're getting stronger, you know...
我想这就是我们变得越来越强的原因
because we're working it out, getting buff.
因为我们一直在锻炼 身体越来越棒了
Buff.
身体越来越棒
How about this for a workout?
把它用来健身怎么样?
Holy shit!
天呐!
That was awesome.
太好了
Classy.
太帅了
Mm-hmm. Attractive.
嗯 太棒了
I think it's time we took this out of the backyard.
我想是时候大干一番了
Stop, stop, stop. Right here. This is perfect.
停下 就是这儿 太完美了
- Really?  - This is it.
- 真的吗?  - 就是这儿了
Matt. Yah!
马特 瞧好了!
Let's get this one.
就她了
Whoa! Hey! Hello!
哇! 嘿! 回来!
- Hey, what  - Andrew.
- 嘿 怎么  - 安德鲁
Help! Somebody grab that!
帮帮忙! 谁来拉它一把!
Whoa! Whoa! Stop!
哇! 哇! 停下!
- Okay, I'll get the top. I'll get the top.  - Got it. Got it.
- 好了 我来拿上面那个  - 拿到了
- Let's get the legs.  - Okay. Wait.
- 摇一下大腿  - 好的 等等
I'm flying!
飞起来啦!
She's just looking at it.
她在朝它看呢
What you looking at, girl? Stay in school!
小姑娘 看什么看? 快回学校去!
Okay, see the guy chewing the gum?
看到那个嚼口香糖的小子了吗?
I'm gonna get the gum and pull it right out of his mouth.
我要把口香糖从他嘴里拔出来
Okay, I got him.
控制住他了
Oh!
哦!
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Why are we running? We don't need to run.
等等 我们为什么要跑啊? 没必要啊
- Five  - I don't want to do it.
- 五  - 我不想这么做
- Four  - Dude, I don't want to do it.
- 四  - 哥们儿 我不想这么做
- You're creating a scene.
- 别丢人了
- I don't want to do it.  - Come on, Matt.
- 我不想这么做  - 快点吧 马特
Don't be a bitch about it. Just do it. .
别婆婆妈妈的了 快点
Put your hand on the table
快把手放桌子上
- Okay. Are you ready? Do it.  - Give me a countdown.
- 好了吗 准备好了? 开始吧  - 你数三二一啊
- I will. I promise...  - Ow!
- 知道了 我保证...  - 哦!
Oh, snap!
哦 咔嚓!
- Like I said...  - You gotta pay for that now.
- 我就说吧...  - 你要被他打了
Like I said. See?
我说了吧 看到没?
Holy crap.
老天爷啊
Just pretend there's a barrier over your hand, right?
就好像你手上有了层护甲一样 懂吗?
When things are gonna hit you, as long as you're ready...
不管什么东西打你 只要你有所准备...
they will not hurt you because of the barrier.
这层护甲就不会让那东西伤害到你
That's so sick.
这太变态了
That's me right there.
那类型可是我喜欢的
Steve, Steve, you have to try this, dude. Give me your hand.
史蒂夫 史蒂夫 你一定要试试看 伙计 把手给我
- Let's go, move.  - But do you guys share cups on the team?
- 算了 我们还是走吧  - 你们在一起的时候 还公用一个杯子的嘛?
No, we don't share cups, man.
才没有 我们才没用一个杯子 伙计
You see that car though?
你看到那车了吗?
- The red one.  - Yeah.
- 那辆红的  - 看到了
All right. The gum was cool.
这样吧 刚刚口香糖那出很酷
All right. You tried. It was a failed attempt though.
好吗 虽然没试成功 起码你试了
Watch this.
看好了
- What are you doing?  - Watch.
- 你要干什么?  - 看着就行
No, no, no...
别去 别去...
What?
什么?
No way!
不会吧!
Holy shit!
老天爷!
Dude! Holy crap!
大哥! 我的天啊!
What! What!
天啊! 天啊!
- That's what I'm talking about!  - Did anybody see?
- 这才是我说的!  - 没人看见吧?
Steve Montgomery for president!
请支持史蒂夫 蒙哥马利做学生会主席!
- I'm having, like, a face period.  - Oh, man.
- 我就好像... 脸上来月经了一样  - 哦 伙计
Pause.
停一下
You guys. You guys, here she comes.
大伙 快看 她过来了
- Here she comes!  - Oh...
- 她过来了!  - 哦...
Don't look. Don't look, don't look...
别朝那边看 别朝那边看...
Steve, don't look.
史蒂夫 别朝那边
She can't find... She thinks it's stolen.
她找不到了... 她肯定以为被偷了
- She has no idea...  - Yes, it was the black guy this time.
- 她完全迷茫了...  - 没错 这次是这个黑人干的
I could have sworn I parked it right here. Where is my car?
我发誓我是停在这里的 我的车去哪里了?
Ignore us.
不用理我们
We're just... Mormons.
我们只是... 摩门教的
What does that mean?
这个是什么东西?
Uh-oh! Uh-oh!
啊哦! 啊哦!
Garetty's... Garetty's having a giggle fit.
Garetty... Garetty的笑太奸诈了
That was so... It was amazing.
刚刚太... 太刺激了
I know. Just take it easy with the merchandise.
我知道 别拿车里面的东西过瘾啊
How did nobody see that? It was out in the open.
怎么没有人看到呢? 那可是在露天啊
Her face! I cannot get her face out of my mind!
她那个表情! 我脑子里全是她那个表情!
That was awesome.
那太好玩了
Who is this?
后面那个谁啊?
So many ideas of stuff that we can do!
我们想到什么就能做什么了!
- Go around.  - That's just some redneck asshole.
- 走开  - 就是群乡下佬而已
- Go around.  - Steve, Steve...
- 走开  - 史蒂夫 史蒂夫...
Take the camera. Take the camera.
拿着摄像机 拿着摄像机
All right. Just make sure it's zoomed out all the way.
好了 注意焦距要对准啊
- Got ya. I can see you.  - Okay, buddy.
- 好的 我对准你了  - 好了 伙计
What you gonna do?
你要做什么?
What the hell is this guy's problem?
这人脑子有毛病吧?
What are you doing?
你要做什么?
Abracadabra!
看招!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Andrew.  - Oh, shit!
- 哇哦 哇哦 哇哦! 安德鲁  - 哦 见鬼!
What the hell did you just do? Matt, stop the car! Stop! Stop!
你他妈刚刚做了些什么? 马特 停车! 停车!
- Are you crazy?  - Pull down the road. We gotta go down there right now.
- 你疯了吗?  - 靠边停下 我们赶快下去看看
Guys, I'm sorry!
大伙 对不起了!
What did you do? Why did you do that?
你到底做了什么? 你干嘛要这么做?
I didn't mean to. I didn't...
我不是故意的 我不是...
Shit! What the hell is wrong with you? Look at this!
见鬼! 你他妈脑子出了什么问题? 看看你做的好事!
- Will you just calm down!  - The guy's probably still in there!
- 你冷静一下!  - 那人可能还在车里面!
I'm sorry, okay?
是我错了 好吗?
- Andrew, stop, stop!  - But I can... I can help!
- 安德鲁 别下去! 别下去!  - 但我能... 能帮上忙!
- I can get him out.  - Stop doing things!
- 我能把那人救出来  - 你什么都别动!
Steve! Steve!
史蒂夫! 史蒂夫当心!
Steve, be careful!
史蒂夫 小心点!
Shit! Shit!
见鬼! 见鬼!
Oh, my God, Andrew. Are you kidding me?
老天爷啊 安德鲁 你是在开玩笑吗?
Steve!
史蒂夫啊!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
老天啊 老天啊
Goddamn it!
见了个鬼!
Steve!
史蒂夫啊!
- Andrew!  - Oh...
- 安德鲁 你没事吧!  - 哦...
Shit!
见鬼!
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
擦 擦 我擦!
Oh, Matt, he's got him! He's got him. He's got...
哦 马特 救出来了 他把他救出来了 他...
Help me.
帮我一把
I'll get in back of him.
我从后面拖
Get him up.
把他拉上来
Hang on. Steve, stay with him. I'm gonna go get some help.
坚持一会儿 史蒂夫 陪在他旁边 我去找人帮忙
- Are you calling the cops?  - Yeah, yeah.
- 你是要报警吗?  - 是啊 是啊
- Will you stop? I can't hear them.  - Will you hang up the phone?
- 你闭嘴行吗? 我听不见手机里的声音了  - 你能把电话挂了吗?
- Yeah. It's just down past, uh, White Crescent Bridge.  - Matt, he's fine.
- 是的 就是在过了White Crescent桥后面一段路  - 马特 他没事了
- Matt, he's fine.  - Yeah. Yeah.
- 马特 他没事了  - 是的 是的
- Fine, Matt!  - Stop! Stop! I can't hear...
- 他没事了 马特!  - 别吵! 别吵! 我听不到...
Hey!
嘿!
Hey! Hey! Over here!
嘿! 嘿! 在这边!
Peeled off the road and went straight through the guardrail.
就是滑出了马路 直接冲向护栏了
Hey, is that on?
嘿 摄影机开了吗?
This is a game or something?
这对你来说是个游戏吗?
I don't understand how you guys can be so angry.
我不知道为什么你们这么生气
You don't understand how we can be angry?
你不知道我们为什么这么生气?
Andrew, you... you put somebody in the hospital tonight, okay?
安德鲁 你... 你今天害的那个人要住院了 好吗?
Do you understand that?
你明白这点吗?
Andrew, look at me. You put a guy in the hospital!
安德鲁 你看着我 你害的那个人要住院了!
How do you feel about that? You hurt somebody!
你难道没有点内疚吗? 你伤害到别人了!
- Shit!  - We need rules, okay?
- 见鬼!  - 我们需要约法三章 懂吗?
Rule No.1, No using it on living things.
第一条 超能力不能用在活物上
Rule No.2, You can't use it when you're angry. That's it.
第二条 生气的时候 不得使用超能力 没商量
Rule No.3, I don't think we should be using it in public
第三条 我觉得我们不应该在公共场合使用能力
or telling anybody about it.
或者告诉其他人
Look, you can't just declare rules, okay?
听着 你不能就这么定下规则啊 懂吗?
I will declare rules...
这规则我就定下了...
You're the one that said that nothing matters.
你自己说的无所谓的
I will declare rules.
我就定下这规矩了
If we're gonna keep going, and we're getting stronger, we need rules.
如果我们这样下去 我们会变得更强 那我们就需要守些规矩
We need rules, right?
我们需要规则 没错吧?
Matt's right. We need rules.
马特说的没错 我们需要些规则
Andrew! Answer the goddamn phone!
安德鲁! 他妈的接电话啊!
Andrew!
安德鲁 接电话!
Matt, what did you say?
马特 你说什么?
Are you still mad at me?
你还在生我的气吗?
- No, I'm not mad.  - Well, you seem mad.
- 没有 我没在生气  - 你看上去就是在生气
I'm not mad. I just...
我不是生气 我只是...
I just think that we need to be more careful now, you know? We can't...
我只是觉得 我们应该更小心了 懂吗? 我们不能...
We have to think a little bit more. We can't just do things.
我们要多动动脑子 我们不能没动脑子就去做事情
We have to think first, okay?
我们要三思而后行 好吗?
- I understand.  - Okay.
- 我知道了  - 好的
Why is Steve out in the boonies?
史蒂夫到这荒郊野外的干什么啊?
Where are we?
我们这是在哪里?
Steve?
史蒂夫 在吗?
His car's right there.
那不就是他的车吗
- Yeah.  - Steve, where you at?
- 是啊  - 史蒂夫 你在哪里?
Steve!
史蒂夫啊!
Look up.
看上面
Hello, boys.
你好啊 小伙子们
What?
什么?
- What is up?  - No. No.
- 怎么了啊?  - 不会吧 不会吧
Wait, guys. Wait, wait, wait. Check me out. Hear me out.
等一下 伙计 等等 看着 看我的
- You're flying!  - Holy shit!
- 你这是在飞啊!  - 我了个擦!
- Wait, wait, wait. Hear me out. Hear me out.  - No way! No way!
- 等等 等等 听我说完 听我说完  - 不可能! 不可能!
What are you doing?
你在做什么啊?
It's much easier than it looks. I swear. It's much easier than it looks.
这比看起来简单多了 我发誓 这没看起来这么复杂
Oh, my God, dude.
老天爷啊 伙计
Make sure you catch yourself. Don't try and jump...
确保你提住自己 别只试着跳起来...
- or you'll just flip yourself.  - I got it. I got it.
- 要不然会摔个狗吃屎的  - 我知道了 我知道了
- Come on, Matt. Come on.  - All right.
- 快点 马特 快点  - 好的
Oh, shit!
哦 见鬼!
Oh, man!
哦 伙计!
- Eating dirt, man.  - Why don't you get behind me?
- 啃泥了吧 伙计  - 你为什么不站在我后面呢?
- You were in my way.  - What do you mean, I was in your way?
- 是你妨碍我了  - 我妨碍你了 这算什么意思啊?
Think Harrier jet. Think Harrier jet.
想想鹞式喷气机 想想鹞式喷气机的原理
Oh, man.
哦 伙计
- Goddamn it!  - Are you okay?
- 见了个鬼!  - 你没事吧?
- I'm watching.  - Just let me concentrate.
- 我旁观而已  - 让我专心一下
- Focus! Focus!  - Okay! Hold on.
- 专心! 专心!  - 好了! 继续吧
Is that your focus face?
你专心起来就这样子?
Oh, my God, dude.
老天爷啊 伙计
- Whoo!  - Bullshit!
- 哇哦!  - 不可能!
- I'm up! I'm up!  - Are you kidding me?
- 我飞起来了! 我飞起来了!  - 你这是在开玩笑吗?
- Holy crap!  - Hold it! Hold it!
- 我的天啊!  - 保持住! 保持住!
- Oh, my God, dude. I am doing it.  - Holy crap, dude.
- 老天爷啊 伙计 我做到了  - 我的天啊 伙计
- Yeah!  - That's it, man. You're doing it.
- 好极了!  - 就是这样子 伙计 你做到了
Whoo-hoo...
哇哦...
- Okay. Okay.  - Andrew, don't fart. We'll never find you again.
- 好的 好的  - 安德鲁 千万别放屁了 不然我们就找不到你了
Steve, stop me. Stop me, stop me.
史蒂夫 让我停下来 让我停下来
- Oh, my God.  - Whoa, whoa.
- 我的天啊  - 啊哦 啊哦
- You are flying now.  - You guys look so cute together.
- 你飞起来了  - 你们这对看起来帅极了
- Whoa!  - I'm coming up. I'm bringing the camera, okay?
- 哇哦!  - 我来了 摄像机我也带上了 没问题吧?
All right.
好的
All right. How do we get down?
好吧 我们怎么下去呢?
- Whoo-hoo!  - Yeah!
- 啊哦!  - 爽啊!
Andrew! It's freezing up here!
安德鲁! 上面冻死人了!
I can't hear you.
我听不见
Activate hyperdrive!
超光速系统启动!
Whoo!
哇哦!
Where the hell are we?
我们这是在哪里啊?
- Catch up! Let's go!  - What?
- 快跟上! 我们出发!  - 什么?
Whoo! This is insane!
哇哦! 这太疯狂了!
Whoo-hoo!
哇哦!
- Dude!  - All right, Andrew!
- 大哥!  - 没事的 安德鲁!
Whoo!
哇哦!
- Tag, you're it!  - Watch out.
- Tag 到你了  - 当心点
- Pump the brakes!  - Whoa! Aah!
- 急刹车了!  - 哇哦! 啊!
Hey, Matt! You're finally good at something!
嘿 马特! 你终于有所长了!
It's so easy! Yeah!
这也太简单了吧! 好哎!
- Aah!  - Yeah!
- 啊!  - 好极了!
Whoo!
哇哦!
Whoa!
Got it!
我接到了!
Tebow time, baby!
蒂博时刻 看招! （蒂博 美著名橄榄球运动员）
Yeah!
好的!
- Oh!  - Nice hands, Steve!
- 哦!  - 接得好 史蒂夫!
- Touchdown!  - Throw it back to Daddy!
- 触底得分!  - 看大哥接这球!
Oh, dude. Nice catch, man! Yes!
哦 伙计 接的好啊! 好球!
- Steve! Go deep!  - Hey, Matt!
- 史蒂夫! 扔远点!  - 嘿 马特!
Do you hear that?
你听见了吗?
What is that?
什么东西的声音?
Steve!
史蒂夫啊!
Oh, shit. Almost died, dude. Holy shit. Holy shit.
哦 见鬼 差点死了 伙计 见鬼 见鬼
Almost died, man! Almost...
差点就死了 伙计! 差点啊...
Andrew, you saved my life!
安德鲁 你救了我的命!
Oh, my God. You saved my life!
老天爷啊 你救了我一命!
Oh, God, you saved my life!
Oh, my God!
我的天啊!
- Okay.  - Holy shit.
- 够了  - 我的天啊
Is that the camera? You saved me and the camera?
那是摄像机吗? 你救了我还有那相机?
Please tell me you got that on tape! You have to...
千万告诉我这些都录下来了! 你一定要...
- Ah, shit.
- 啊 见鬼
- What the hell...  - We're alive!
- 见什么鬼...  - 我们活下来了!
- What the hell happened?  - You didn't see what happened?
- 他妈刚刚发生了什么?  - 你没看见发生了什么?
Oh, shit! Andrew! Andrew! You're a genius!
我擦! 安德鲁! 安德鲁! 你就是个天才!
We got to see this! Holy...
我们要看一遍! 我的...
All right. Oh. Holy shit.
好了 哦 我的天啊
Wait. Oh, God! We're on the ground. Yes!
喘口气 我的天啊! 我们踩在陆地上了 好极了!
Whoo!
哇哦!
We have broken history!
我们肯定打破历史记录了!
I mean, I'm talking about since the caveman times.
我指的是 自从洞穴人那时候开始的
Uh, the Egyptians, the Wright brothers.
那埃及法老啊 怀特兄弟啊
Come here, Matt. Come here. Get in here. Get in.
过来 马特 过来 到镜头前来 过来
Say it, I can fly.
说 我飞起来了
- I can fly.  - I can fly!
- 我飞起来了  - 我飞起来了!
- Oh, come on.  - Say it with your chest!
- 哦 拜托  - 大声的吼出来!
- I can fly!  - Say it, Matt.
- 我飞起来了!  - 大声点 马特
- Shout it out!  - I can fly!
- 咆哮吧!  - 我飞起来了!
I can fly! I can fly!
我飞起来了! 我飞起来了!
I tried to save you, man. Andrew was just quicker.
我是打算救你的 伙计 只是安德鲁动作快了点而已
How does that go again?
要不我们再来一次?
We almost died.
我们差点挂了
- Oh, please.  - Gestures...
- 哦 别提了  - 看这姿势...
How does she not notice though?
她怎么还没注意到我呢?
Come on. Let's be serious, guys.
拜托 老兄 说真的
She definitely noticed that it's gotten better.
她肯定注意到你变好了
- You just gotta be, you know...  - Yeah?
- 你只要 只要...  - 怎样?
You just gotta be subtle.
你只要表现得让人捉摸不透
That is so cool.
那会很给力的
Dude. And I haven't had sex since summer.
兄弟们 我从夏天开始就没做过爱了
I haven't had sex since ever.
我从来就没做过
- Really?  - Really?
- 不会吧?  - 不会吧?
- That is completely unacceptable.  - Well...
- 这完全无法接受啊  - 好吧...
How are you guys so cool? How are you guys so cool, man?
老兄 你们怎么就能那么爽呢? 怎么就能那么爽呢?
Liquid nitrogen.
请用爽身粉
Hey, guys?
嘿 兄弟们?
Guys? You guys up?
兄弟们? 你们还醒着吗?
Yeah.
醒着
Hey, uh... today was like...
嘿 呃... 今天是...
It was like, I think, the best day of my life.
我觉得 今天是我这辈子最棒的一天
Like, I mean...
像是...
I'm thinking about it, and I can't think of any day...
我一直在想 想不出任何一天...
that I liked better than today, you know?
能比今天更酷 你们觉得呢?
I really... I think it was.
我真的... 真的这样想
Yeah.
没错
Unanimous.
想法一致
Yes.
是啊
Okay. Good.
没错 很棒
Okay, check this out. Say what you want...
快想想 你们都有什么想做的...
But I'm thinking about booking it to Maui for the weekend.
我倒是想周末飞去毛伊岛
- What's up with that?  - Seriously?
- 你们觉得怎么样?  - 说真的?
Well, we could do it. I mean, I was thinking the same thing...
我们可以的 我也这样想过...
except I've always wanted to go to Tibet.
不过我想去西藏
- Why Tibet?  - Tibet?
- 为什么?  - 去西藏?
Yeah. I don't know.
是啊 我也不知道
It seems really beautiful, you know, with all the...
感觉那里很美 那里有...
Will you shut up? Shut...
你能不能闭嘴? 闭嘴...
- The monuments and mountains, you know?  - Mm-hmm.
- 那里有很多古迹 山脉 知道吗?  - 嗯哼
I don't know. And the monks have achieved such a high level of enlightenment...
还有啊 那里僧人的佛法修为非常高深...
that they can, like, float and shit, you know?
高深到他们也能飞啊什么的 知道吗?
- So we would fit right in. - We could really mess with their heads as well.
- 我们就找到同类了  - 我们还可以耍耍他们
Yeah, but, like, seriously, I think we should go.
但是 说真的 我觉得我们应该去
It would be really cool. Peaceful.
会很棒 内心能平静下来
No, I think it's a really good idea. I actually would like to go.
我觉得不错 我真的想去
I'm down. You down, Steve?
我同意 你呢 史蒂夫?
What... I... I don't know, man.
什么... 我... 我不知道
There's no bikinis in Tibet. So I don't know if I'm down with that.
西藏没有比基尼美女啊 所以我决定不了
Oh, hey. Sorry, I just...
哦 嘿 不好意思 我...
Hi.
嗨
Do you mind if I film you?
介意我拍你吗?
Uh, a little bit. I don't really like being on camera actually.
呃 有点 我不太喜欢被拍下来
Well, maybe it's, like, exposure therapy.
也许 可以当这是暴露疗法
Yeah. No, I just came by to give you something actually.
哦 其实我是顺路过来 给你点东西
- You did?  - Yeah.
- 真的?  - 是啊
What?
是什么?
I was watching your, um...
我一直关注你的 呃...
your... you know, your blog?
你的... 博客?
There's a drought in the Central African Republic, right?
中非正在闹干旱 对吧?
Yeah. So I saw that and I thought it seems pretty cool, and it's cheap too...
我觉得捐款也没多少钱 而且可以积德...
so I thought why not?
所以为什么不捐呢?
- Totally.  - Yeah.
- 没错  - 是啊
Yeah, I can tell that you're really global and big picture...
我觉得你很关注世界问题 而且...
- concerned about that kind of stuff.  - Yeah.
- 能顾及他人  - 是啊
You know, Matt, you can just mail this yourself.
马特 你可以自己寄过去的
I'm not your mom.
我不是你妈妈
Okay. I mean, I just...
好的 我只是...
What is this? Is this, like, the new you?
这算什么? 算是一个全新的你?
You got too smart to have fun in eighth grade. So now what?
你那么聪明 跟小孩子玩没什么乐趣 所以来找我?
No.
不是的
Casey, Casey, Casey, Casey, Casey, Casey.
凯茜 凯茜 凯茜 凯茜 凯茜 凯茜
Listen, listen. Can I just talk to you for a second?
听我说 听我说 能占用你一点时间吗?
- Can I just tell you something?  - Mm-hmm.
- 我有话跟你说 可以吗?  - 说吧
I just... I... l...
我只是... 我... 我...
I just want you to know I'm not, you know, who I was... now.
我想让你知道 我已经... 不是从前那个我了
- You know, I'm cool. I'm just...  - You're cool?
- 我现在很厉害 我...  - 很厉害?
High school popularity just seemed like this weird backward contest...
在我看来 在学校受不受欢迎这种事 毫无意义...
and I thought since I knew that, I could just...
我想通这一点后 就觉得...
That made you better than everybody else.
就觉得你自己比任何人都优秀
No. No, no, no.
不是的 不 不 不
- I know what you mean.  - I would separate myself from that.
- 我明白你什么意思  - 我只是想说 我和别人不一样
- I get it.  - You get it?
- 我明白  - 你明白?
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼
I know it sounds weird. I just wanted you to know that.
我知道这听上去很奇怪 但我只是想让你知道
To know that you're cool.
知道你很厉害
Wow, I really screwed this up.
哦 看来我搞砸了
Not as much as you might think.
或许并非你想的那样
- Really?  - Good-bye.
- 是吗?  - 拜拜
- Casey...  - I gotta go. Bye.
- 凯茜...  - 我还有事情 拜拜
Come on.
拜托
Dude! When did you start doing this?
老兄! 你什么时候会这样玩了?
- Like, since when?  - What, with the camera?
- 什么时候?  - 你是说 让摄像机飞起来?
- Yes, with the camera.  - Um...
- 是啊 让它飞起来  - 呃...
I don't know. It's been a little while, I guess.
我也不知道 我想有一段时间了吧
See... Oh. I can't do that.
这样... 哦 我就做不到
I can't do stuff that requires finesse.
这种需要施展巧劲的 我就做不到
I tried to type my name out yesterday, and I cracked my keyboard in half.
我昨天想打自己名字 结果把键盘弄成了两半
No, dude. It's really easy. You just... you think that you're holding it.
不会吧 很简单的 你只要... 想象是自己拿着它
Whoo!
喔!
See, it's different, 'cause you've always had friends...
我们不同 是因为你有很多朋友...
and people want to talk to you and be around you.
大家都喜欢跟你说话 在你周围
I never had any of that. I mean, before this...
我一个朋友也没有 我是说 在这之前...
I barely even hung out with Matt, and he's my cousin.
我也很少和马特出去玩 他还是我哥
We were close when we were little, but...
我们从小很亲 但是...
I don't know. In high school, everything changed.
我也不知道 上了高中 一切都变了
You know, I've been meaning to ask you.
我一直想问问看你
Winter break is coming up.
快放寒假了
You should do the talent show with me.
你应该和我一起参加才艺秀
No way.
不可能
Why not? It'd be good for you to get out there, you know.
为什么? 这样你就可以融入进来了啊
- Meet some people, meet some girls.  - Dude, I'm not... It's just not...
- 多认识点朋友 还有姑娘们  - 老兄 我不行... 不能...
- What?  - Look, I'm just really shy, okay?
- 怎么了?  - 我一直很内向 好吗?
And I don't... I don't even have any talents, so...
还有我... 我没有任何才艺 所以...
What are you talking about, you don't have... you have talent.
你在说什么啊 你怎么会没有... 没有才艺
You've got talent.
你已经有了啊
Oh, dude, no way.
哦 老兄 别开玩笑了
You look handsome.
你看上去真帅
Thanks, yes. Steve...
谢谢 是史蒂夫...
let me borrow some of his clothes...
把他的衣服借给我...
to make me look cool or whatever.
让我看起来不错
I'm glad you're spending so much time with your friends.
看到你和朋友们在一起 我很高兴
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
是啊 我也很高兴
- Hey.  - What?
- 站住  - 怎么了?
How are you getting to school?
你怎么上学去?
- I don't know what you mean.  - Don't bullshit me, you idiot.
- 什么意思  - 别想耍我 你个白痴
Matt doesn't come. He doesn't drive up.
马特没过来 没人开车
You leave the house. Who the hell's giving you rides to school?
你出了门 谁带你去学校?
- M... Matt.  - All right. You know what?
- 马... 马特  - 当我不知道吗?
You're lying.
你在撒谎
You're up to something, and you can't hide it.
你在搞什么名堂 别想瞒着我
You think you can just slink, hmm?
你以为你能蒙混过去?
Sneak in, sneak around my house, smiling?
鬼鬼祟祟 进进出出 嬉皮笑脸?
I'm onto your shit.
你拉什么屎我都知道
How do you even work this stupid thing?
这东西是怎么玩的?
Ah! And we're in business.
啊! 开始干正事了
Boo!
!
- Hey.  - Hi.
- 嘿  - 嗨
Um, what are you doing here?
呃 你在这儿干嘛?
I'm filming for the talent show.
为才艺秀摄像
- Matt Garetty is filming for the talent show.  - Yes, I am.
- 马特・贾雷提在为才艺秀摄像  - 没错
Wow.
哇喔
What is this, some kind of newfound school spirit?
这算什么 某种新的学校精神?
How do you like it, huh? Being on camera?
你觉得怎么样? 被拍进来怎么样?
- I actually don't mind being on camera.  - Oh. Here we go.
- 我不介意被拍啊  - 哦 好戏上演了
Ladies and gentlemen, now coming to the stage...
女士们先生们 即将上台的是...
- What? No philosophical comeback for me?  - Steve Montgomery.
- 怎么了? 不对我进行哲学复原了?  - 史蒂夫・蒙哥马利
You're probably gonna want to get this on camera.
你肯定很愿意把这个拍进去
All my underclassmen, come on. Make some noise. That's not loud enough.
台下的新生们 让我听到你们的声音 还不够大声
How about my upperclassmen? Come on. Make some noise!
高年级的同学呢? 来吧 让我听到你们的声音!
Yeah, Steve!
耶 史蒂夫!
Let me hear it from my seniors, class of 2012!
让我听听2012级同学们的声音!
Yeah. Shh.
太棒了 嘘
Now I want you guys to give it up for the young and very talented Mr. Andrew Detmer.
现在 请给我们年轻的天才安德鲁・德特摩尔先生 来点掌声
- And you're on.  - Come on, y'all.
- 到你了  - 来吧 掌声
- What are you guys doing?  - Let's go, let's go!
- 你们想干嘛?  - 掌声 掌声!
Are you playing a prank on your cousin?
你们在耍你弟弟吗?
That's mean, Matt.
马特 你们太坏了
Just watch.
只管看吧
Really?
不会吧?
- Good luck!  - What's he doing?
- 好运!  - 他要干嘛?
Show us some talent!
把你的才艺秀出来!
Nice, Matt.
干得不错 马特
Fifty-two, Pickup! Pick 'em up!
52张 全部捡起来! 捡起来!
No way!
不可能!
Yeah!
耶!
Whoo!
哇喔!
Go, Andrew!
加油 安德鲁!
What? What?
不是吧? 不是吧?
- Are they gonna walk on that?  - What do you think?
- 他们要走在上面吗?  - 不然你觉得呢?
- Whoa.  - He's got it. He's got it. He's got it.
- 喔  - 他可以的 他可以的 他可以的
Easy.
放轻松
Yeah, you got it.
没错 你可以的
Holy crap!
天呐!
Yeah! Cakewalk!
耶! 高空步!
Give it up, give it up, give it up!
掌声 掌声 掌声!
Oh, my God. Andrew is so amazing.
哦 天呐 安德鲁太酷了
Whoa!
哇喔!
Give it up! Let's go!
掌声! 来点掌声!
- Seriously, how are they doing this?  - I don't know.
- 说真的 他们怎么做到的?  - 我不知道
Magic.
魔术
Whoo!
喔!
- That was amazing!  - Yeah!
- 简直太棒了!  - 耶!
Whoo! Whoo! Andrew!
喔! 喔! 安德鲁!
- Oh, my God. I can see your head is, like, exploding right now.  - What?
- 哦 上帝啊 我能看出你的脑袋 就要爆炸了  - 什么?
This is the beginning of your downfall. Hubris. Right there.
你现在开始狂妄了 当心要堕落了
- What's hubris?  - Ha, ha, ha.
- 狂妄是什么?  - 哈 哈 哈
- No, what does "hubris" mean, Matt?  - Seriously?
- 不是 "狂妄"是什么意思啊 马特?  - 你是认真的?
- What does "seriously" mean?  - What? I'm...
- "认真"又是什么意思?  - 什么? 我...
- Get in there.  - Don't push me, dude. I'm going.
- 快进去吧  - 别推我 老兄 我在走呢
Your fans await. You're the man of the hour.
你的粉丝们等着呢 你可是风云人物
- Look at this house!  - Oh, sick!
- 看看这别墅!  - 哦 太酷了!
- Dude, this place looks huge.  - I know.
- 老兄 这里真是太大了  - 是啊
- It's enormous.  - Dude.
- 大极了  - 老兄
Matt! Andrew!
马特! 安德鲁!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!  - Steve! Oh, my God!
- 哦 天呐! 天呐!  - Steve! 上帝啊!
- Everybody's freaking out.  - Come on, man. Everybody's been waiting for you.
- 大家都疯狂了  - 快来 大家都在等你
V.I.P coming through. Coming through!
贵客到! 贵客到!
Andrew Copperfield coming through!
大魔术师安德鲁来了!
Make way, make way.
让出路来 让出路来
Matt, come this way. Drew, over here.
马特 这边 德鲁 这边
Andrew Detmer's in the house!
安德鲁・德特摩尔驾到!
- How are you feeling?  - I'm... I'm... I'm doing good.
- 感觉如何?  - 我... 我... 感觉还行
- Yeah? Are you sure? Are you sure?  - Hey. Hey.
- 是吗? 确定吗? 确定吗?  - 嘿 嘿
- Hello.  - Andrew.
- 你好啊  - 安德鲁
- Magic is so hot.  - Oh, wow. Thanks.
- 你的魔术太性感了  - 哦 哇喔 谢谢
- So, do you not remember me at all?  - Um...
- 你一点都不记得我吗?  - 呃...
- Monica, right? Monica.  - Yes!
- 莫妮卡 对吗? 你是莫妮卡  - 是我!
Setting the camera down. I'm setting the camera down.
把摄像机摆好 让我把摄像机摆好
- What...  - Oh.
- 怎么...  - 哦
- Oh.  - Excuse me.
- 哦  - 借过一下
Have you ever played that, over there?
你玩过那边那个吗?
Uh, no. I have never played that, over there.
呃 没有 我从来没玩过
- No?  - Never.
- 没玩过?  - 从来没有
- I bet you're good at it.  - Uh...
- 我猜你肯定玩得很好  - 呃...
- What, you just throw the ball into the cups?  - Yep. Yep.
- 是什么 把球扔进杯子里?  - 是啊 是啊
- I actually could be good at that right now.  - Yeah?
- 我现在应该蛮擅长的  - 真的?
- Maybe.  - Let's find out.
- 也许  - 我们去试试
- No, no, no, no, no.  - Come on!
- 不 不 不 不 不  - 来吧!
- What?  - Come on.
- 不会吧?  - 快来
- Okay, okay.  - Come on.
- 好吧 好吧  - 快点
Okay, I'm coming. I'm coming.
好吧 我来了 来了
There you are.
找到你了
Amazing.
太棒了
That's what I'm talking about.
和我说得一样
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
耶! 哇哦!
Hey, where is Andrew anyway?
嘿 安德鲁去哪儿了?
Oh.
哦
Andrew's upstairs with the girl with the pink hair.
安德鲁在楼上 和那个粉色头发的女孩儿在一起
What, like, they went together?
什么 你是说 他们一起上去的?
That's my boy. Of course they went together. What are you talking 'bout?
他是我的兄弟 当然一起上去的 你想说什么?
Hey, Andrew. I hope you're seeing this.
嘿 安德鲁 希望你能看到这段
Congratulations, sir.
恭喜你 先生
I just wanted you to know, dude...
我只是想让你知道 兄弟...
I was really worried about you before all this, you know?
在这之前我一直在担心你 知道吗?
But, dude, things are gonna get so much better for you now.
不过 兄弟 从今以后一切都会好起来的
I really, really feel that.
我真的这么觉得
And I want you to know I love you, you know?
我想让你知道我爱你 你知道吗?
I love you, man. It's you and me.
我爱你 兄弟 你和我是一家人
It's Detmer and Garetty, extended family for life.
德特莫尔家和贾雷提家 是永远的大家庭
- Oh, sorry. Sorry.  - No, man. Excuse yourself.
- 哦 抱歉  - 不 兄弟 没事
Oh, man.
哦 兄弟
- When did I become the one who's out here filming myself?  - Hey, Matt.
- 我什么时候变成呆在这儿玩自拍的人了?  - 嘿 马特
Oh, hey. Hey, Casey.
哦 嘿 凯茜
So what are you filming?
你在拍什么?
Uh, it's just a thing.
呃 只是随便拍拍
It's not like eye of the storm or anything.
不是什么焦点速报之类的
Hey, I wanted to... I wanted to tell you...
嘿 我想过要... 想过要告诉你...
I've really been... it's been making me think a lot.
我真的是... 我想了很多
I've been kind of thinking about it in my...
我好像真的觉得它在我的...
No, I have. Like, in my life.
不 我说真的 在我的生活中
I've been thinking, if I applied myself, what I could do.
我一直在想 如果我能加把劲 我能做到什么事
I could really... I could change the world.
我或许真的可以... 我可以改变世界
- I mean, it's really been...  - You're drunk.
- 我是说 这真的已经...  - 你喝醉了
What?
什么?
Hey, Casey?
喂 凯茜?
I've basically been stalking you since, like, sophomore year.
我大概是从大二开始注意你的
Sorry, use of the word "stalking." I shouldn't have said...
对不起 用了"注意"一词 我不该这么说的
You want to get out of here?
你想出去走走吗?
- Yeah.  - Yeah?
- 想  - 是吗?
Yes. Yes, definitely.
是 是的 当然
Uh, I have to drop off the camera first though.
呃 不过我得先把摄影机还回去
Okay, you guys are getting ready to witness history, all right?
好了 大家有没有准备好见证历史的时刻?
I'm like a proud dad right now because behind these doors...
我现在就像是一个自豪的老爸 因为在这扇门背后...
Andrew Detmer becomes a man.
安德鲁・德特莫尔要成为男人了
He's a little boy behind there. He's scared.
他是个小男孩 呆在里面 他很害怕
He's like a butterfly, getting ready to emerge...
他像是只蝴蝶...
- Oh, God!  - from a cocoon or some shit like that.
- 哦 天呐!  - 亟待破茧而出
Disgusting weirdo!
恶心的怪胎!
- Wait. What happened?  - Ha... ha. Okay...
- 等等 发生什么了?  - 呵呵 好吧...
- Is that...  - Out of my way now!
- 难道说...  - 别挡我的道!
- Oh, man.  - Monica, what happened?
- 哦 兄弟  - 莫妮卡 发生什么事了?
Drew! Drew! It's okay, man. Don't worry about it.
德鲁! 德鲁! 没事的! 兄弟 别担心
- Look, it happens to the best of us, okay?  - Dude!
- 听着 这事在每个人身上都可能发生的 明白吗?  - 兄弟!
You had a little too much to drink...
你喝得有点多了...
- You...  - Oh. Oh. Whoa, buddy.
- 你...  - 哦 哇哦 兄弟
- The hell's going on, dude?  - Why are you laughing?
- 发生什么事了 兄弟?  - 你怎么在笑?
Aw, man. All over my jacket.
哦 兄弟 还都弄到了我的外套上
- Stop. Stop laughing.  - What are you talking about?
- 停下 别笑了  - 你在说什么?
- It's cool, man.  - No, it's not cool, Steve. Stop.
- 这很酷 兄弟  - 不 一点都不酷 史蒂夫 别这样了
- Stop what? It's cool, man.  - Will you just get out of here?
- 别什么? 这很酷啊 兄弟  - 你能不能给我出去?
- Get out! What's your problem?  - Drew, Drew!
- 出去! 你有病吗?  - 德鲁 德鲁!
- You think this is funny?  - No, I'm not laughing...
- 你觉得这很好玩吗?  - 不 我没在嘲笑你...
Get out!
出去!
Dad!
爸爸!
Andrew! Please! I need my medicine.
安德鲁! 求你了! 把药给我
Mom's in pain, all right? She needs her pills! Where are you?
母亲很痛苦 明白吗? 她需要药! 你在哪儿?
Where are you?
你在哪儿?
Dad!
爸爸!
Hoarding a $500 camera while your mom dies in there? I mean, how selfish can you be?
你妈快死了 你却藏了个500美元的摄影机? 我是说 你怎么能这么自私呢?
I went through your camera.
我看了看你拍的东西
What did you see?
你看到了什么?
Just you being a loser.
就看到你是个窝囊废
You think that those people are your friends?
你把那些人当做自己的朋友吗?
Huh? They're not.
哈? 他们不是
You're an embarrassment.
你是个耻辱
You're running around this town, spending my money.
你在镇里瞎晃 挥霍我的钱
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
看着我说话!
I didn't spend any of your money, Richard.
我没花过你一分钱 理查德
'Cause I don't have a dime to spend.
因为我没钱给你花
Every last cent... Look at me!
每一分钱... 看着我!
- Every last cent goes to school for you...  - School?
- 每一分钱都供你上学用了...  - 学校?
- and medication for your mother.  - I go to a public school!
- 还有支付你母亲的医药费  - 我上的是公立学校!
- I can't even pay for a goddamn...  - You don't pay for a public school, you idiot!
- 我连一个该死的...  - 公立学校不需要你付学费的 你这蠢货!
What did you call me?
你叫我什么?
Did you call me an idiot, you shit?
你叫我蠢货吗 你这个畜生?
Did you call me an idiot? Huh?
你叫我蠢货了吗? 啊?
You piece of shit!
你这狗娘养的畜生!
Get up. I said get up!
起来 我说了 起来!
Get up!
起来!
- I could crush you, you know that?  - Stop it!
- 我可以剁了你 你知道吗?  - 停下!
- Crush you!  - Get...
- 剁了你!  - 叫上...
Smile, Matt.
微笑 马特
- Oh, my God, Matt.  - Oh.
- 哦 天呐 马特  - 哦
Can we not do the camera thing right now, please?
我们能不能先停止拍摄一会儿 拜托了?
What happened?
发生什么事了?
Uh... it just started out of nowhere.
呃... 不知从哪儿冒出来的
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
My head hurts really bad.
我头很痛
That's probably Steve calling your cell again.
可能又是史蒂夫打给你的
I'll call him back later.
我晚点回拨给他
I think it's time to take...
我想该是去...
Hey! Hey, asshole!
嘿! 嘿 混蛋!
What are you doing up here?
你在那儿干什么?
Just leave me alone, Steve!
别管我 史蒂夫!
You can't be up here, dude. This isn't safe.
你不能上去的 兄弟 那儿不安全
I don't want to talk to anyone.
我不想和任何人说话
Bro, what are you doing up here?
兄弟 你在那儿做什么?
Leave me alone!
别管我!
How did you find me?
你是怎么找到我的?
I don't know, man. My nose was bleeding.
我不知道啊 兄弟 我的鼻子在流血
I heard your voice or something like...
我听到了你的声音 像是...
What the hell happened to your face?
哦 你的脸怎么了?
Nothing, man. Just leave me alone.
没事的 兄弟 别管我了
Well, that's not nothing. That... Your dad!
哦 这可不是没事 是... 是你爸!
Your dad beat the shit out of you. He can't do that to you now.
是你爸爸把你打成这个这幅样子的 他现在不能再这么对你了
Will you stop acting like you give a shit?
你能不能不要这么假惺惺的?
Dude. Why are you talking to me like this? I'm your best friend.
兄弟 你为什么老是这么和我说话? 我是你最好的朋友啊
I don't have any friends!
我没有朋友!
You were never my friend before any of this.
你从来都不是我的朋友
I hang out with you and Matt, like, every day!
我每天都和你还有马特一起出去!
We're supposed to fly around the world together. Don't you... Do you remember that?
我们还打算一起周游世界的呢 难道... 难道你都忘了吗?
- You think I'm... -  Stop! Just stop talking to me!
- 你觉得我...  - 住嘴! 不要再说了!
- Why won't you just leave me alone?  - Come on, man.
- 你为什么不能让我一个人呆会儿?  - 过来 兄弟
Steve, I'm telling you, get away from me!
史蒂夫 我警告你 离我远点!
Get away from me now! Please!
离我远点 立刻! 求你了!
who, by the power of God, are safeguarded in faith.
诚心祈愿的人 将得到神的庇佑
Even though you do not see him now...
尽管现在你无法与他相见...
you rejoice with an indescribable and glorious joy...
在你的信仰之目标实现时...
as you attain the goal of your faith...
在你的灵魂得到救赎时...
the salvation of your soul.
你将得到难以言表的莫大欢愉
What are you doing? You filming graves?
你在干什么? 是在拍墓地吗?
- I don't get it.  - What do you care?
- 我不明白  - 你在乎什么?
You haven't been returning my calls. Why aren't you returning my calls?
你都没有回过我电话 你为什么不回我电话?
- I've been busy.  - No, you haven't.
- 我一直很忙  - 不 你一点都不忙
Why aren't you returning my calls?
你为什么不回我电话?
I just don't feel like talking.
我只是不想跟人说话
- Turn off the camera.  - No.
- 把摄影机关掉  - 不要
Andrew. Andrew, turn off the camera.
安德鲁 安德鲁 把摄影机关掉
Andrew? How did he get struck by lightning...
安德鲁? 这场暴风雨并没有雷击记录...
during a storm with no recorded lightning strikes?
他是怎么被雷击中的?
How?
怎么被击中的?
And they found Steve out in the middle of a field.
而且他们是在田野中发现史蒂夫的
Why would Steve go out in the middle of a field during a lightning storm, Andrew?
为什么发生暴风雨的时候 史蒂夫会跑到田野里去呢 安德鲁?
- I don't know.  - Why? What?
- 我不知道  - 为什么? 什么?
I don't know what happened, Matt!
我不知道发生了什么 马特!
I don't believe you, okay? I don't believe you.
我不相信你 好吗? 我不相信你
- I want you to turn off the camera and talk to me.  - Why?
- 我要你把摄影机关掉 回答我的问题  - 为什么?
- 'Cause I want to have a conversation with you.  - Don't tell me what to do, Matt.
- 因为我想跟你好好聊聊  - 不要指使我该做什么 马特
You can't tell me what to do! Don't ever tell...
你不能对我指手画脚! 想都别想...
- Give me... Shut it off!  - Get off of me!
- 快给我... 关了它!  - 放开我!
Andrew... are you joking right now?
安德鲁... 你现在是在开玩笑吗?
Is this a joke to you? I...
这对你来说是个玩笑吗? 我...
What did you do, Andrew?
你做了什么 安德鲁?
What did you do?
你做了什么?
Who am I supposed to tell about this?
我应该找谁谈谈这事?
Who do I talk to? Who do I talk to about this?
我应该找谁谈谈? 我应该找谁谈谈这事?
Why won't you just tell me what happened, Andrew?
你为什么不能告诉我那天发生了什么 安德鲁?
Please believe me, Steve.
请相信我 史蒂夫
Please, it's just I...
求你了 这只是我...
I don't know what I did. I...
我不知道自己干了什么 我...
I lost control, and...
我失去了控制 然后...
and I'm so sorry.
我对不起你
This thing is just becoming a part of me now...
这能力如今已经成为了我的一部分...
and I don't...
而我也无能为力...
I miss you, Steve.
我很想你 史蒂夫
all the drills. Good. We're all pretty good, right?
所有的训练 很好 我们都表现得不错 对吗?
Get ready. Go!
准备 上!
You guys? Do not hesitate.
兄弟们? 不要犹豫啊
Did you hear who worked?
你听说是谁做的吗?
He was like...
他就像是...
Oh! Oh, Andrew!
哦! 哦 安德鲁!
Dry off!
擦擦干!
Totally.
当然
Hey, Wayne!
嘿 韦恩!
Okay, so, see this one here?
好吧 看到这颗牙吗?
This one I got really clean 'cause I did this little, like...
这颗看起来很干净 因为我... 在拔出来的时候...
lasso thing around the root, you know?
在牙根处利用了套索原理 明白吗?
But then these two...
不过这两颗...
these, I did not get as good.
我就没拔好
See how they're broken?
看到它们是怎么断的吗?
I think it's because I got them from the middle, you know, instead of the root.
我想可能是因为我是从中间而不是根部拔出来的
Oh. Oh.
噢 噢
Oh. Sloppy.
哦 真脏
I've been doing a lot of reading, you know, like, online about, like...
知道吗 我一直都大量阅读 知道吗 好像 在线阅读之类的
just like evolution and, like... and natural selection...
会读一些有关进化论的 像是... 自然选择之类的...
and how, like, there's this thing, right?
还有 像 有种东西 对吗?
It is called the apex predator, right?
叫顶级掠食者 对吗?
And basically what this is is the strongest animal in the ecosystem, right?
基本上 这应该算是生物系统中最强的生物了吧?
And as human beings...
而作为人类...
we are... we're considered the apex predator...
我们... 我们被认为是顶级掠食者...
but only because, like, smaller animals can't feed on us...
但只是因为 像是 一些小动物无法以我们为食...
because of weapons and stuff, right?
因为我们有武器什么的 对吗?
The lion does not feel guilty when it kills a gazelle. Right?
当狮子杀死一头羚羊时 它是不会感到罪恶感的吧?
You do not feel guilty when you squash a fly.
当你拍死一只苍蝇 你也不会有罪恶感的吧
And I think that means something.
我觉得这说明了一些问题
I just think that really means something.
我只是觉得这真的意味着什么
This one I got really clean cause I did this little, like...
这颗看起来很干净 因为我... 在拔出来的时候...
lasso thing.
利用了套索原理
Andrew, what happened at school? Huh?
安德鲁 学校里发什么了什么? 啊?
- I need to go and pick up my mom's medication!  - Oh, yeah?
- 我得去学校给我妈拿药!  - 哦 是吗?
You're gonna break the rules again? We're too strong for that now, Andrew!
你又想打破规则了吗? 我们现在太强大了 安德鲁!
- If you did that, you know what I'd have to do!  - You'd have to what?
- 如果你那么做 你知道我必须得采取措施了!  - 你要干嘛?
- You have to start thinking.  - What would you have to do, Matt?
- 你得想清楚  - 你要干嘛 马特?
There are consequences to what you do!
你的所作所为会招致报应的!
- You could not do anything to me because I am stronger than you.  - Stop that bullshit!
- 你什么都别想干 因为我比你强大  - 闭上你的臭嘴!
I know what you did. I'm not gonna let you do it again!
我知道你的所作所为 我不会再让你为所欲为下去了!
I am not going to break your stupid rules! Okay?
我不想去打破你那白痴的规则! 好吗?
So just screw off and stay out of my life!
只要你滚出我的生活就好!
I can't breathe.
我不能呼吸了
Thank you.
谢谢
- Karen Detmer.  - Just one moment.
- 凯伦・德特莫尔  - 请稍等
We're gonna need a next-day delivery.
这药我们明天才能配送
Co-pay on that is $750.83.
价钱是750.83美元
- Well, I don't have all that.  - Son, I told your dad, and I'll tell you.
- 哦 我没钱  - 孩子 我告诉过你父亲 现在我再和你说一遍
You can pay up front, and we can order next-day delivery.
你可以预付 我们明天会配送
- Other than that, I can't help you.  - Prick.
- 否则 我就帮不了你了  - 混蛋
Oh!
哦
Hey.
嘿
Hey!
嘿!
- Give me all your money.  - Uh, what? Who is that?
- 把你的钱都叫出来  - 啊 什么? 你是谁?
Doesn't matter who it is. Just give me all your money or else.
我是谁不重要 把钱都交出来就行了
Or else? Shit, man.
否则? 妈的
Shit, man. Is that Andrew?
妈的 伙计们 那是安德鲁吗?
It sounds kind of like Andrew under there.
听着有点像
And you got Andrew's broke-ass backpack on.
而且还背着安德鲁破烂不堪的双肩包
- Oh, you got a gat?  - I got a gat too, bitch.
- 哦 你有枪是吗?  - 我也有 白痴
Dude!
老兄!
Whoa, dude!
喔 哥们!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
快点 快点 快点 快点 快点 快点!
Come on, come on, come on!
快点 麻烦快点 再快点!
Hey!
嘿!
The camera needs to stay on for our investigation.
这个摄像机需要留给我们调查
Jesus Christ.
天呐
Can I have a moment alone with my son?
我能和我儿子单独待会吗?
If he regains consciousness, notify the officer outside.
如果他恢复知觉 通知外面的警察
Yeah, yeah.
好的 好的
Oh!
哦!
Your mother's dead.
你妈妈死了
She died last night while I was out looking for you.
她死时我正在外面找你
I came home, and, uh...
我回到家 然后 呃 ...
she was there in her bed.
她就躺在床上
If I just could have been there for her.
如果我待在那陪她就好了
I was always there for her when you were out screwing around.
你在外面鬼混的时候我一直陪在他身边
And this one time...
然而这次...
this... one time...
这次... 仅仅一次...
that she needed me, and you took me away!
她需要我时 我却在外面找你!
I want you to apologize to me.
我想要你给我道歉
I know you can hear me, so I want you to sit up right now...
我知道你能听见 我要你立刻坐起来...
and apologize to me.
然后给我道歉
You selfish, selfish asshole!
你个自私鬼 自私的混蛋!
This is your fault!
这都是你的错
You...
是你...
Do you hear me?
你能听见吗?
Your mother is dead, and it is your fault!
你妈妈死了 是你造成的!
Happy birthday!
生日快乐!
Pound it? Pound it?
击拳? 击拳?
Go and get a present. Go and get a present. Yeah.
去拿个礼物 过去拿礼物 是的
- Yes, the big one.  - Oh, my God. Matt.
- 对 就是那个大的  - 哦 我的天呐 马特
Matt, your nose again.
马特 你的鼻子又流血了
Are you okay?
你还好吗?
- Oh, shit!  - Baby, you're really bleeding.
- 哦 该死!  - 宝贝 你真的在流血
- Matt, your nose! Oh, my God.
- 马特 你的鼻子! 哦 我的天呐
Did you hear that? How can you not hear that?
你听到那个吗? 你怎么会听不到?
- Hear what? What are you hearing?  - It's so...
- 听到什么? 你在听什么?  - 好像是...
- Something's wrong with Andrew.  - Casey, come in here!
- 安德鲁出事了  - 凯茜 到这来!
We apologize for the delay, but as of right now...
我们为延误报道向您道歉 但是 截至目前...
- every news helicopter in Greater King County...  - Oh, my God.
- 大半个西雅图的新闻直升飞机...  - 哦 我的天呐
Is headed to Seattle.
正在前往
Again, right now, we have very little information...
重复一遍 目前 我们信息不足...
but it appears a bomb has gone off at Ballard Community Hospital.
但是看上去好像是巴拉德社区医院遭到炸弹袭击
Casey, come here. Come here. Come here. Please. Please.
凯茜 到这来 到这来 过来 快点 快点
- What? No, Matt. Are you seeing this?  - Where are your keys at?
- 什么? 不 马特 你没看到这个吗?  - 你的钥匙呢?
- What? Matt...  - Just stay here. I'll be back.
- 什么? 马特...  - 就待在这 我马上回来
- I just have to drive there, okay?  - Please, wait! Matt, please!
- 我得开你车去 可以吗? - 等等! 马特 求你等等!
- Listen, Andrew's in trouble, okay?  - Andrew's what?
- 听着 安德鲁有麻烦了 知道吗?  - 安德鲁怎么了?
I'm sure that Andrew is fine.
我肯定安德鲁很好
- Andrew needs me! I need to get to the city.  - Tell me what's going on.
- 安德鲁需要我! 我得去市区  - 告诉我怎么回事
Shit. I gotta get... Is that a roadblock?
该死 我必须... 那是个路障吗?
Nobody else is driving this way! Talk to me!
这条路上没人! 告诉我怎么回事!
- Casey, stop! I need to think, okay?  - Stop!
- 凯茜 先别说话 我得想想办法 好吗?  - 停下!
I gotta find another way downtown. Shit!
我必须另找一条去市中心的路 该死!
Go back and take the Madison exit.
倒回去 从麦迪逊出口过去
Come on.
快点
- Stay here, Casey. Stay here.  - Wait!
- 待在这里 凯茜 待在这  - 等等!
Matt, wait for me!
马特 等等我!
All units, report to Ballard Community Hospital.
各单位请到巴拉德社区医院报到
Excuse me.
打扰了
Sir, excuse me.
警官 打扰一下
Matt! What are we doing here?
马特! 我们来这干嘛?
Oh, my God!
哦 我的天呐!
You gotta put me down! Please! Stop!
你必须放我下来! 求求你 住手!
You did this to me!
这就是你的报应!
Matt! Oh, my God!
马特! 哦 我的天呐!
Holy shit! Holy shit!
天呐! 天呐!
- Matt!  - Casey, we gotta go! We gotta go right now!
- 马特!  - 凯茜 我们得跟上! 我们立刻出发!
Get in the car! Let's go.
快上车! 我们走吧
- Andrew's out of control.  - What are you talking about?
- 安德鲁失控了  - 你在说什么?
- I'm so sorry. I wanted to tell you. I...
- 我很抱歉 我早想告诉你的 我...
Oh, my God, Matt! Stop the car!
哦 天呐 马特! 快停车!
It's gonna crash. Holy shit!
快撞上了 天呐!
Oh, shit!
哦 该死!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.  - Get off the road now!
- 对不起 抱歉  - 立刻从车上下来!
Oh, my God!
哦 我的天呐!
Hold on to me!
抓住我!
- It's not me, it's Andrew!
- 不是我干的 是安德鲁!
- Hold on!
- 抓住了!
I can't stop it! I can't control the car! I can't control it.
我停不下来! 我无法控制这辆车! 我控制不了
Shit!
该死!
Andrew! Oh, God, hold on!
安德鲁! 哦 天呐 抓牢了!
- Hold on to me!
- 抓住我!
I can't get the door open!
车门打不开!
- Oh, my God!  - Andrew! Andrew, stop!
- 哦 我的天呐!  - 安德鲁! 安德鲁 住手!
- Casey!  - Matt!
- 凯茜!  - 马特!
Matt!
马特!
Help me!
救我!
Casey, hold on!
凯西 抓住!
Matt.
马特
Stay here. Okay? You have to stay here. Okay?
就待在这 好吗? 你必须待在这 知道吗?
Matt, please don't go! Matt!
马特 求你别离开我! 马特!
We got a car on fire under the Needle. Possible casualties.
方尖塔下面有辆车着火了 可能有人员伤亡
We need emergency response now.
我们现在需要应急响应
I don't know how to describe this.
我不知道该如何描述这个
That is the Needle we're looking at, and as you can see, there are...
这就是我们正在关注的方尖塔 正如你所见 那有...
You're not gonna believe this.
这个真是难以置信
Are you seeing this?
你看到了吗?
Back away from the window!
远离窗户!
What the hell are they doing up there?
他们到底在这干嘛?
Get down!
趴下!
Seventeen, beware.
十七号 当心点
You're gonna have to divert.
你必须掉头
Andrew! Andrew, look at me!
安德鲁! 安德鲁  看着我!
This has to stop right now, okay? This is really, really bad!
你必须马上停手 知道吗? 这样真的非常非常糟糕!
Why did you catch him?
你干嘛要接住他?
- Listen! Just focus, okay?  - I dropped him!
- 听着! 集中注意 好吗?  - 我把他扔下去!
- Why did you catch him?  - Andrew, this is not a game!
-- 你为什么要接住?  - 安德鲁 这不是游戏!
Do you understand? You're hurting people.
你明白吗? 你正在伤害别人
You're weak, Matt! You're all weak!
你很弱 马特! 你们都是弱者!
- Andrew...  - I'm stronger than all of this!
- 安德鲁...  - 我强过一切!
Andrew, listen to me, okay? Just-Just... I need you to listen.
安德鲁 听我说 可以吗? 我只要... 我要你听着
Just focus for a second.
只要集中一会儿注意力
Do not tell me what to do!
不要命令我该做什么!
I'm trying to explain. I got two individuals.
我也难以解释 我看到两个人
- They can't stop us. It's not too late for us to go.  - It is too late!
- 他们无法阻止我们 我们现在跑还来得及  - 太晚了!
I'm done! It's over!
我完了! 一切都完了!
You treated me like shit! You left me alone!
你把我当成狗屎! 你留下我一个人!
Andrew, you're not alone up here! I'm here with you!
安德鲁 你不是一个人! 我在这陪着你!
I should have been with you all along! But I'm here now!
很抱歉我没至始至终陪着你! 但是我现在在这!
And we can stop this right now, you and me!
我们可以立刻停止一切 你和我一起!
Andrew, we can just fly away. We can get out of here.
安德鲁 我们可以飞走 我们能突出重围
We can be family.
我们可以成为一家人
Andrew. Andrew, look at yourself.
安德鲁 安德鲁 看看你自己
- This isn't who you are.  - I'm an apex predator.
- 这不是真正的你  - 我是终极捕食者
What?
什么?
I'm an apex predator.
我是终极捕食者
No! No!
不! 不要!
Oh, my gosh! Call the police!
哦 天呐! 快叫警察!
Andrew, no!
安德鲁 不要!
Oh! Whoa!
哦! 哇!
Paul! Paul, stay away from the window!  - Okay, okay!
保罗! 保罗 离窗户远点!  - 好的 好的!
- Paul! Don't stand at the window!  - Are you seeing this? Hey!
- 保罗! 不要站在窗户边!  - 你看到了吗?
Stay down, babe! Stay down!
蹲下 宝贝! 快蹲下!
Andrew!
安德鲁!
Two subjects down. One injured, one mobile.
两个人都落地了 一个受了伤 另一个还在活动
Andrew? Andrew, look at me.
安德鲁? 安德鲁 看着我
This is all gonna be fine. You're gonna be all right, okay?
一切都会好的 你会没事的 知道吗?
I'm gonna get you help, okay?
我会帮助你的 好吗?
All units, respond Code 4 to Denny Way.
所有单位 回应代码4 去丹尼尔路
Get out of here! It's not safe!
离开这! 这不安全!
Andrew? Andrew?
安德鲁? 安德鲁?
- Are you getting this?  - Don't move!
- 你看到了吗?  - 不许动!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
不要开枪! 不要开枪!
Hold on! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! I need help! I need help!
等一下! 等等 等等 等一下! 帮帮我! 我需要帮助!
He appears to be held at gunpoint, but...
他好像被警察控制住了 但是...
Oh, my God!
哦 天呐!
Arms up in the air!
举起手来!
Don't shoot, please!
请不要开枪!
He's hurt!
他受伤了!
- Get on the ground!  - Wait! Wait!
- 趴在地上!  - 等等! 等等!
- Do what he says!  - Now, get down!
- 照他说的做!  - 喂 趴下!
- Do not get up!  - Get on the ground!
- 不许起来!  - 趴在地上!
- Please don't shoot!  - We will shoot you!
- 请不要开枪!  - 我们要开枪了!
- I'm not gonna do anything!  - Whoa, whoa, whoa! The glass!
- 我不会做什么的!  - 哇哇哇! 看那些玻璃片!
Take him out!
干掉他!
Leave me alone!
别烦我!
Shit!
该死!
Whoa! Whoa! Wow!
哇! 哇! 哇!
We have multiple explosions.
这有多起爆炸
- Get in position!  - We have 'em in our sights!
- 各就各位!  - 我们能看到他们!
We're covered! Hold it right there!
有人掩护我们! 在那别动!
No! Stop!
不要! 住手!
We have you surrounded!
我们已经包围了你们!
- No!  - Hands where we can see 'em!
- 不要!  - 把手举起来!
Stay down! Stay down!
趴下! 不许动!
- Stay down!  - I repeat, do not move!
- 趴下!  - 我再重复一遍 不许动!
Additional units on the far side!
新增机组包围侧面!
Yo, stay down!
喂 蹲下!
Stay down! Don't move!
蹲下! 不许动!
Andrew! Andrew!
安德鲁! 安德鲁!
Stop! Don't hurt them!
住手! 不要伤害他们!
Andrew!
安德鲁!
Andrew! Andrew, stop!
安德鲁! 安德鲁 住手!
Please, stop!
求求你 住手!
Andrew!
安德鲁!
Don't make me do this!
不要逼我!
Stop!
住手!
reports of casualties.
人员伤亡报告
At least two structures have been destroyed.
至少有两栋建筑物被毁
I think they're both down!
我想他俩都倒下了!
Two men out.
两个人都倒下了
Show me right now eastbound on...
往东行的车辆立刻去现场...
Yes, sir. I'm about two blocks away. I see it.
好的 长官 我再过两个街区就到了 我明白
Move up.
快上
Hey! Oh! What are you doing?
嘿! 哦! 你干什么?
Hey, Andrew.
嘿 安德鲁
I just wanted to say that...
我只想说...
I'm sorry and, uh...
对不起 呃...
I... I hope...
我... 我希望...
that you know that I did what I had to do.
你能明白我的所作所为
You're not a bad person. I know that.
你不是一个坏人 我坚信不疑
That's all that matters.
就是这些
And, uh, I want you to know...
还有 呃 我想告诉你...
that I'm gonna be better from now on.
从今往后 我会努力变得更好
I'm gonna help people.
我会去帮助别人
I'm gonna find out what happened to us down there.
我回去查明我们在那个洞里到底发生了什么事
I don't care how long it takes.
我不在乎这要花多长时间
I'm gonna get answers.
我一定会弄明白
I'm gonna do it for you, and I'm gonna do it for Steve.
我将会为你和史蒂夫找到答案
And...
还有...
I just...
就是...
I love you, man.
我喜欢你这个人 兄弟
I didn't ever get a chance to tell you...
我一直没有机会告诉你...
but I love you.
但是 我的确喜欢你
And guess what.
然后 猜猜看
You made it.
你做到了
Whoo-hoo!
喔-哦!
Isn't it beautiful?
很漂亮 不是吗?
Good-bye, Andrew.
再见 安德鲁
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
协调：心仪Sally
翻译：死神夜月 Flower一休 RK翔 小粥粥 slowly回声 hangubing
校对：心仪Sally 淡定哥
超能失控